mytrustmark.com 2013-04-16

# Trustmark Banking and Financial Solutions

## To print this privacy policy, please download the full privacy policy in Adobe Acrobat format (PDF) by clicking here.

| 

### **WHAT DOES TRUSTMARK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
---|---  
  
## Why?

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
## What?

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security number and income
  * account balances and payment history
  * credit history and credit scores

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  

## How?

| 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Trustmark chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
### **Reasons we can share your personal information**

| 

### **Does Trustmark share?**

| 

### **Can you limit this sharing?**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**For our everyday business purposes—** **  
** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| 

YES

| 

NO  
  
**For our marketing purposes—** **  
** to offer our products and services to you

| 

YES

| 

NO  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

YES

| 

NO  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—** **  
** information about your transactions and experiences

| 

YES

| 

NO  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—** **  
** information about your creditworthiness

| 

YES

| 

YES  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

YES

| 

YES  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

NO

| 

NO  
  
| 

  * Call 1-800-844-4357 

**Please note:**  
If you are a _new_ customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
  
---|---  
  
## Questions?

| 

Call 1-800-844-4357   
  
### **Who we are**  
  
---  
  
**Who is providing this notice?**

| 

Trustmark National Bank  
  
### **What we do**  
  
**How does Trustmark protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. 

We restrict access to your personal and account information to those associates with proper authorization to access such information.   
  
**How does Trustmark collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you 

  * open an account or apply for a loan 
  * make deposits or withdrawals from your account 
  * use your credit or debit card
  * apply for insurance

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus.  
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only 

  * sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness 
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you 
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you 

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.   
  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

| 

Your choice will apply to everyone on your account.  
  
### **Definitions**  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.   
The Trustmark Corporation Family of Companies:    
Trustmark National Bank; Trustmark Investment Advisors, Inc.; Fisher Brown Bottrell Insurance, Inc; Somerville Bank & Trust Company                                            
  
**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * do not share

**Joint marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * our joint marketing partners can include institutions such as insurance companies
